

Contact



0404 652 859



wolfgang.stueckle@gmail..com



Melbourne, VIC



Portfolio Page



Github



Linkedin

Key Skills

- C/C++
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- JavaScript
- React
- Node/Express
- MongoDB
- Flask/SQL

Non Technical Skills

- Software project management
- Leading and training of apprentices
- Raising my 2 children as a single dad
- Time management

Wolfgang Stueckle

Software Engineer

I'm a seasoned professional with expertise in software development, project management, and electrical engineering. I've spent more than ten years running Wolf Electrical, managing electrical projects like solar PV system installations and training apprentices. Previously, I worked at Robert Bosch in Germany and Australia, developing software for engine control systems and addressing production issues.

I hold a Bsc in Electrical and Electronics Engineering and a higher diploma in IT from the Academy of Information Technology/Coder Academy. In the future I plan to enhance my skills in embedded systems programming and AI.

Experience

O 2012 - 2022

Wolf Electrical

Business Owner

- Planning and installation of solar PV systems
- Completion of several new builds, multi units and private houses in required timeline
- · Home entertainment, data cabling, smart wiring
- Fault finding, debugging of control circuits
- Trained 4 Apprentices in all levels

2007 - 2012

Robert Bosch Pty Ltd, Melbourne, Australia

Production and test engineer

- Find root cause of production issues, implement actions to avoid re occurrences.
- New product introduction (NPI), production release of test stations and software.
- Improvement of final test equipment, cycle time and yield rate.
- Test and release of software for final testers in C.

2000 - 2006

Robert Bosch Germany and Australia

Project management and Software development engineer

- Project organisation
- Responsibility for software project budget and timing.
- Developed engine control software and series introduction for production for Projects of Holden and Suzuki in C and Assembler

Languages

- German, Native speaker
- English, Fluent in reading and writing
- Japanese, Conversational
- French, Conversational

Education and Qualification

2023

Academy of information technology/ Coder Academy

Higher diploma of Information Technology

2023

UDACITY

Nanodegree in C/C++

2012

Holmesglen TAFE, Melbourne

Certificate IV in Electrical- Photovoltaic Systems

1996 - 1999

HSR or University of Applied Sciences Rapperswil/ Switzerland

Bsc in electrical and electronics engineering

References

Available on request